<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Top5SanDiego</string>

    <!-- Rank number String Variables -->
    <string name="rank_1">1)</string>
    <string name="rank_2">2)</string>
    <string name="rank_3">3)</string>
    <string name="rank_4">4)</string>
    <string name="rank_5">5)</string>

    <!--Name of the locations in EatsFragment-->
    <string name="eats_born_and_raised">Born and Raised</string>
    <string name="eats_born_and_raised_description">Spacious, modern destination for high-end steak
                                                    and cocktails with glitzy decor and a rooftop patio.</string>
    <string name="eats_tofu_house">Tofu House</string>
    <string name="eats_tofu_house_description">Big portions of hot stone Korean BBQ, tofu stews and
                                                sides amongst no-frills decor in a strip mall.</string>
    <string name="eats_tajima">Tajima</string>
    <string name="eats_tajima_description">Since we first opened in 2001, Tajima has been satisfying
        San Diego\'s growing hunger for authentic Japanese cuisine and ramen that is both unique and
        flavorful. Thanks to owner Sam Morikizono and his talented staff, Tajima has earned a
        reputation as one of San Diego\'s top Japanese restaurants.</string>
    <string name="eats_city_taco">City Taco</string>
    <string name="eats_city_taco_description">City Tacos has turned up the heat on innovative,
        delicious and unique bites. We prepare fresh Mex as it should be… “con sazón!” You’ll find a
        special blend of positivity and seasoning here that makes our food pop! Born in San Diego’s
        North Park neighborhood, City Tacos now proudly serves the communities of La Mesa and
        Imperial Beach. Our three locations are dedicated to combining traditional recipes with SoCal
        flavor to make our tacos unique. Meat, fish, vegetarian, even Paleo offerings offer something
        for every taste. Our dishes can also be topped with a variety of creative salsas to customize
        each bite. At the end of the day, we believe that food should be a celebration</string>
    <string name="eats_eureka">Eureka</string>
    <string name="eats_eureka_description">Our first San Diego restaurant is located at the
        University Town Center. This all-American scratch kitchen doesn’t just stop with their
        handmade gourmet burgers and menu using locally sourced produce. Eureka!’s small batch
        whiskey, extensive rotating craft beer and beverage program is something all beer lovers
        will enjoy. With a stacked weekly calendar they provide a one-of-a-kind experience for
        guests with half off wine Tuesdays, Steal The Glass Wednesdays, Live Music Thursdays, a
        daily “Hoppy Hour” and weekend brunch. If you’re looking for a place with all-American food,
        the best craft beer selection and the best whiskey bar in San Diego, then Eureka!, you’ve
        found</string>

    <!--Name of the locations in NightLifeFragment-->
    <string name="bar_onxy">Onxy</string>
    <string name="bar_onxy_description">Experience the best of San Diego nightclubs at Onyx Room.
        Located in the heart of downtown San Diego, Onyx Room brings world class DJs, a fun,
        vibrant dance club atmosphere, and the best bottle service San Diego has to offer.
        Make a reservation today.</string>
    <string name="bar_the_local">The Local</string>
    <string name="bar_the_local_description">The Local Eatery and Drinking Hole opened its doors in
        2003, as a family owned and operated restaurant and bar. Mina Desiderio saw an opportunity
        to carve out a niche in the Financial District of Downtown San Diego. The philosophy was
        simple: Bring the beach and all things that define San Diego to downtown. The vision was to
        be an establishment that supported local sports teams, local cuisine, local beers,
        local music and local events, hence the name, The Local.</string>
    <string name="bar_el_prez">El Prez</string>
    <string name="bar_el_pres_description">Our rooftop overlooks Pacific Beach. Our gourmet tacos
        are made with fresh, local ingredients and served in house-made tortillas. Our bar features
        a large selection of tequilas, with 18 beers on tap. We have 24 HD TVs and a giant projection
        screen. There’s no place on the boardwalk like us. Our bar was built on the concept of Dia
        de los Muertos. Combine all of these elements, and El Prez is where to drink, where to eat
        and where to party in San Diego!</string>
    <string name="bar_altitude">Altitude</string>
    <string name="bar_altitude_description">erched 22 stories above the historic Gaslamp District,
        ALTITUDE Sky Lounge is an elite rooftop bar in San Diego, pairing stunning panoramic views
        with a sleek, modern atmosphere complete with a blazing fire pit and can’t-miss happy hour.
        The bar offers bottle service; a fine selection of wine, beer and cocktails; an impressive
        array of appetizers, flatbreads, burgers and more.</string>
    <string name="bar_polite_provisions">Polite Provisions</string>
    <string name="bar_polite_provisions_description">Apothecary-esque bar offers craft cocktails and
        microbrews in a stylish, retro space with an atrium.</string>

    <!--Name of the locations in HotelsFragment-->
    <string name="hotel_manchester_grand_hyatt">Manchester Grand Hyatt</string>
    <string name="hotel_manchester_grand_hyatt_description">Surrounded by shops and restaurants
        along San Diego Bay, this high-end hotel is 9 minutes\' walk from the San Diego Convention
        Center and 3 miles from San Diego International Airport.Featuring floor-to-ceiling windows
        with bay or city views, upscale rooms offer free Wi-Fi and flat-screens; studios add pull-out
        sofas. Club rooms provide access to a private lounge serving complimentary breakfast,
        while suites come with kitchenettes and living rooms. Room service is available. Dining options
        include a seafood restaurant, a buffet eatery with a terrace, and a rooftop lounge and bar.
        There\'s also a spa and a gym, as well as 2 outdoor pools.</string>
    <string name="hotel_bahia_resort">Bahia Resort</string>
    <string name="hotel_bahia_resort_description">Set on Mission Bay, this relaxed resort is a
        12-minute walk from Belmont Park and 2.2 miles from SeaWorld San Diego. The simple,
        traditional rooms offer flat-screen TVs and free Wi-Fi, along with coffeemakers and
        minifridges. Some have beach or garden views. Suites add kitchenettes and dining tables,
        as well as sitting areas and bay views. Room service is available. A turn-of-the-century
        riverboat offers free cruises between the resort and a sister property. Dining options
        include a Mediterranean cafe and a Moroccan-themed lounge bar. There\'s an outdoor pool,
        a hot tub and a kids\' game room, along with tennis courts and live entertainment.</string>
    <string name="hotel_hilton_bayfront">Hilton Bayfront</string>
    <string name="hotel_hilton_bayfront_description">Across the street from the San Diego Convention
        Center, this polished 30-story convention hotel overlooking San Diego Bay is a 7-minute walk
        from Petco Park, home of the Padres baseball team, and 10 minutes\' walk from the historic
        Gaslamp Quarter. Airy rooms offer bay and city views, plus flat-screen TVs and Wi-Fi (fee).
        Suites add living areas with pull-out sofas. There\'s an upscale restaurant offering
        innovative global dishes, as well as a sports bar, a coffee shop, and a waterfront bar with
        a terrace. Other amenities include a spa, a fitness center, and an outdoor saltwater pool
        with views of the bay, plus 165,000 sq ft of meeting space.</string>
    <string name="hotel_paradise_point">Paradise Point</string>
    <string name="hotel_paradise_point_description">On a private 44-acre island with a mile of beach,
        this stylish resort is 2 miles from SeaWorld San Diego. Upscale rooms feature flat-screens,
        Wi-Fi and minifridges, plus coffeemakers and patios; some provide bay views. Suites offer
        sitting areas and microwaves, and some add fireplaces and whirlpool tubs. Bungalows offer
        separate sitting rooms and dining tables, and an upgraded suite includes a kitchen. There
        are 5 pools and 4 restaurants, including a breezy waterfront grill, plus a spa, a marina and
        an 18-hole golf course. Additional amenities include a fitness center, lawn games, and
        tennis and basketball courts. Parking is available (fee).</string>
    <string name="hotel_hotel_republic">Hotel Republic</string>
    <string name="hotel_hotel_republic_description">A 5-minute walk from buses, trains and trolleys
        at the Santa Fe Depot, this polished hotel is a mile from shopping and dining at the Gaslamp
        Quarter, and 3 miles from the gardens of Balboa Park. The bright, modern rooms come with
        Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and coffeemakers. Upgraded rooms add sitting areas. Room service is
        offered. There\'s a sleek restaurant and a rooftop bar serving small plates. Other amenities
        include a fitness center and bike rentals.</string>

    <!--Name of the locations in LandmarksFragment-->
    <string name="landmark_balboa_park">Balboa Park</string>
    <string name="landmark_balboa_park_description">Balboa Park is a 1,200-acre urban cultural park
        in San Diego, California, United States. In addition to open space areas, natural vegetation
        zones, green belts, gardens, and walking paths, it contains museums, several theaters, and
        the world-famous San Diego Zoo.</string>
    <string name="landmark_torrey_pines">Torrey Pines</string>
    <string name="landmark_torrey_pines_description">Torrey Pines is a community of 2,600 acres in
        the northern coastal area of San Diego, California, residential with large areas of office
        space along I-5.</string>
    <string name="landmark_san_diego_zoo">San Diego Zoo</string>
    <string name="landmark_san_diego_zoo_description">The San Diego Zoo is a zoo in Balboa Park, San
        Diego, California, housing more than 3,500 animals of more than 650 species and subspecies.</string>
    <string name="landmark_pacific_beach">Pacific Beach</string>
    <string name="landmark_pacific_beach_description">Pacific Beach is a relaxed neighborhood by the
        beach, popular with sunbathers and surfers. Trendy hotel bars and casual cafes line the
        boardwalk, while Mission Boulevard and the surrounding streets are dotted with women’s
        clothing boutiques, yoga studios and casual drinking spots that draw a young, bar-hopping
        crowd. Inland, the grassy slope of Kate Sessions Park has sweeping views of the city and San
        Diego Bay.</string>
    <string name="landmark_mission_bay">Mission Bay</string>
    <string name="landmark_mission_bay_description">Mission Bay is a human-made saltwater bay
        located south of the Pacific Beach community of San Diego, California created from
        approximately 2,000 acres of historical wetland, marsh, and saltwater bay habitat</string>


</resources>
